I can't believe our first day at MIT. MJ,
come on, pretend
like you're not the happiest you've ever
been in your entire life.
I can't. I knew it. Hi, my name is Peter
Parker. You
don't remember me, but we used to know
each other. Something bad
was going to happen, and the only way to
stop it was
to make everyone forget about me. Because
I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider -Man. Put your whimpering. Suit
yourself. Go home.
And sometimes Spider -Man has to do the
hard thing, even if
it breaks Peter Parker's heart. What is
happening to me? Excuse me,
Dr. Banner. I need your help. What did you
say your name
was? If DNA is mutating, it would be
enormously dangerous. Spiders have
three life cycles. When between cycles, it
can leave the spider vulnerable
to threats. We are faced with a danger
that we can't control.
One we can't even see. Stay out of my way.
You're losing
it, kid. And for those spiders who make it
through, it amounts
to a kind of keeper. Nice flowers. Oh,
they're a housewarming gift.
I'm MJ. I'm just a neighbor from across
the hall. Friendly neighbor.
The End.